Dad
You're finally awake
Dr. Wang
My husband's condition...
How bad is it?
Is he getting better?
Director Lin is conscious now
but his bodily functions haven't recovered yet
Right now, he can't speak
His limbs, even his fingers, can't move
We suspect a brain nerve injury
As for the specifics,
we'll need more tests to know
But waking up is a very good sign
I believe he'll recover bit by bit
Try not to worry too much
He'll get better slowly
Okay
Thank you, Dr. Wang
It's my job
I'll be going now
I'll bring Director Lin in for tests tomorrow
Okay, I'll see you out, Dr. Wang
Don't worry, Dad
You'll be better soon
I know, I know
How could I not worry?
He's awake
No, it's just...
He still can't move or speak
But the doctor said he'll recover soon
What if he ends up...
What are you doing? You didn't even make a sound!
You scared me to death
If you've done nothing wrong, what are you afraid of?
Hello? Hello?
What's wrong?
My dad is awake
I'm gonna tell him all the filthy things
you and Jiang Min did
You won't stay smug for much longer
Siqi, your dad just woke up
He hasn't fully recovered yet
If you tell him all that right now,
and his condition worsens,
won't it do more harm than good?
Shut up
You just don't want my dad to get better
Siqi
I know you hate me
You want to kick me out of the Lin family
But, Siqi...
If you really care about your dad,
you shouldn't tell him this now
What you should do is make him happy
Keep his spirits up
That's how he'll recover faster
I'll let you off for now
But you'd better play your part
When my dad fully recovers,
I'll settle the score with you
You're awake
Why didn't you just stay asleep?
Then you could've kept your life
Uncle Sheng, what are you doing here?
I heard your dad woke up
So I came to see him
Is that more comfortable?
Thanks, Uncle Sheng. I'll do it
What's wrong, Dad? Are you uncomfortable?
Your dad can't move or talk
We need to be extra careful caring for him
Try to keep him as comfortable as possible
You're right
I'll be going now
I'll come back
to see you next time
Thank you, Uncle Sheng
Bye-bye
Siqi
I came to see you
and Uncle Lin
Thanks
They're so pretty
But how did you know
I like pink peonies?
I figured you girls
all like this kind of flower
How is Uncle Lin doing?
He's awake
But he can't speak or move
Don't rush it
Got it
Oh, right
Your dad came by last night
Uncle Lin needs care right now
I was worried you'd be overwhelmed
So I looked it up online
For cases like his,
to prevent poor blood circulation
and muscle atrophy,
you need to massage him like this often
to stimulate his nerves
Thank you, Sheng Yuanzhou
If it weren't for you these past days,
I wouldn't know what to do
It's okay
Here, you try
I think my dad moved
I think he really moved
Uncle, try moving again
He really moved!
I'll go get the doctor
Now he can even move his fingers
If he can talk in a couple days,
that damn girl Lin Siqi
will definitely report us
Lin Chengren will definitely divorce me
Don't panic
He's not fully recovered yet, is he?
We still have time
How about we leave?
Leave?
Leave for where?
Even if we leave,
what about afterward?
Then here's what we'll do
While I can still call the shots in the Lin family
We'll sell off every asset we can
Calm down first
Even if he really wakes up
and finds out about us,
you're the mother of his two sons
He has to think of the children
He won't throw you out
Think of the children?
The kids aren't even his
What did you say?
The kids are yours
Then you can never say it, no matter what
Of course I won't
Am I crazy?
I'm just afraid that damn Lin Siqi
will investigate
You don't know how crafty she is
If she ends up...
There won't be any ifs
When did you get here?
Either way, I've heard everything I needed to
The Lin family's money...
You won't get a single cent of it
And starting today,
you two
are getting the hell out of this house
Otherwise,
I'll take my two younger brothers to get a
paternity test
Chairman Sheng, you have to help me this time
We're in the same boat
If Lin Chengren really wakes up,
you'll be...
I'll be what?
Of course you'll be fine
I mean,
I saw it clearly at the scene that day
Lin Chengren fell on his own
I'm just worried if he really wakes up,
he'll bring us unnecessary trouble
Mrs. Lin
As long as you keep your mouth shut,
we'll get through this safely
I understand
Thank you
for coming back with me to get my things
No need to be so polite with me
I hope when my dad sees these things,
he'll recover much faster
Didn't the doctor say so?
It'll definitely be fine
Breakdance Competition Champion
My dad won it when he was in college
He's been bragging about it ever since
I didn't think Uncle Lin was so cool
Everyone was young once
True
How old were you in this one?
About six
So cute
Dad
You have to get better soon
Why are you back again?
I was worried you'd get hungry keeping watch,
so I bought some snacks for you
Thanks
Uncle Lin is moving a lot more than this morning
Don't you think that's a little weird?
What is it?
Uncle Lin's hand
keeps drawing vertical lines
It looks like he's writing numbers
Numbers?
Look
One
Are you writing the number One One One, Uncle Lin?
Maybe my dad can only draw vertical lines now?
Uncle Lin just responded to me
What?
He closed his eyes just now
He did?
I'll ask again
If you're writing the number One One One,
then close your eyes one more time
Look!
One One One
What does One One One mean?
Found it
What?
One One One
Bai Zimei
She's your mom
How could this be here?
So my dad's been guiding us the whole time
to find One One One
It was so we'd
find your mom's medical record
Could it be...
this has something to do with Sheng Shizhong
not letting anyone mention Bai Zimei?
Bai Zimei said the Sheng Shizhong now
isn't her husband,
but the driver, Hu Jin
Hu Jin used the Key of Fate
to become Sheng Shizhong